<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eventually.house</title>
    <link>https://eventually.house/</link>
    <description>Recent content on eventually.house</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 13:35:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://eventually.house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exterior Design (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://eventually.house/post/exterior-design-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 13:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eventually.house/post/exterior-design-part-1/</guid>
      <description>When we first started looking for homes for sale that could become our family home for the long haul, we were dumbfounded by the market: both prices and lack of choice - we had absolutely no intention of undertaking a massive construction project like this. After countless home viewing trips with our realtor (who was great throughout the whole buying process), we started to look at homes outside our price range and it quickly became clear that even if we stretched ourselves financially, we still wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get the kind of home we wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://eventually.house/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eventually.house/about/</guid>
      <description>eventually.house is a journal of the design and build process for a modern energy efficient home in the San Francisco Bay Area. This project started in fall 2019 and the owners are attempting to document the entire process, start to finish. The name comes from disucssions that we were having during the early stages of the project, where seemingly everything we spent our time on was future-looking, always waiting; hence, the project became our &amp;ldquo;eventually house&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Launchpad</title>
      <link>https://eventually.house/post/launchpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 13:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eventually.house/post/launchpad/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2019 my fiancé and I purchased a home in Belmont, California that was originally built in 1946. Our house is in need of a lot of work - the property is not livable in its current state and this blog is our effort to document what will surely be an extensive renovation process, along with navigating and learning about the various big choices we will have to make along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>